Hello and welcome back once again to the
IC Lombard presents Brokers Premier
League 2026. One more encounter, one
more cricketing action. Here we go.
First ball
after the great win from the team one L1
team defeating Ace Diamonds
and that will go all the way. Four runs
first ball.
Soatch
match One loser was a match to loser
live match. Oh, that's clean. Gold gone.
Completely missed it.
Good bowling from Sherish and Kiran
Gaqua departs.
So after two ball four for one ace
diamonds.
Joicket
running.
And that's a good strike from Suraj Rao,
but only a single run at Longone.
Four balls being seven for one. Ace
Diamond versus Unison Superstar. Unison
Superstar won the toss selected to field
first. They invited Ace Diamonds to bat.
And that's a good strike up and over one
bounce
into the fence for four runs at long
off.
Good strike from UD. First ball straight
off the mark with the boundary
power play
and Suraj.
It's only one over power play in the
three overs game.
Last ball will be first over coming up.
Outside edge over the keeper
over the keeper head and that will run
away for four at backward region. So 15
runs in first over age diamonds. One was
gone 15 for one.
Excellent drawing. Two runs taken. They
just uh started the second over
down the track. looking to play for a
big one.
Oh yeah. Bowling inside edge.
Cry again.
Longiel
distance.
Ace diamonds.
That is a big shout to the umpire
playing across the line
and wicket keeper.
All the the players alike in Shah Rukhan
style
posing
for that big appeal but there was no
contact between batten ball.
Only three runs conceded in this over by
the
just going down the left side. Well left
by Sumit.
19 for two.
That will go all the way for four runs.
So eight runs of the door has got one
wicket. Two has gone. 23 for two. Ace
diamonds.
>> three was gone 35 for Chu and 36 to
chase the target innocent superstar
team over Pisto. Oh,
Okay. Request unison superstar batters.
Ace diamonds to set up the field. Yes.
Ace diamonds on the field.
Empire Mr. Om Singh and
Okay, we are all in readiness to start
the second innings. 36 to chase Om on
strike. Nikesh on non-strike and Suraj
will start the proceedings.
Here we go. The first ball. Suraj to Om.
Oh, that's a big flighted ball. And even
keeper has not able to stop that. No
ball and four runs of starting with
freebies.
That's a gift from the bowler.
No ball and four.
Starting with the
extras. Five runs.
Oh, that's clean bold.
But that was free hit.
Just a single and Nikesh now will face
the first ball. Two balls, six for no
loss. 30 to get from 16 balls.
Oh, that's clean ball. Wow, good
bowling.
Totally missed it. Completely beaten
there. And that's
The first wicket fall
Nikesh Golden Duck. Three balls being
gold at 6 for one.
Shashang the new batter.
Oh, that's gone. One more wicket
and that's scored behind.
Second wicker fall. Back to back
wickets.
Suraj Rao on the money.
Four balls being board. Six for two.
Pressure on Unison superstar.
30 runs in 14 balls.
So much uh happening drama in the first
very first tour of the second innings.
They lost two wickets early
and the tension rising in the unison
superstar.
bowling
against
wicket.
One has gone seven for two and 14 ball
left. 29
Second over started by Amul Takur. Back
to back two dot balls.
Once again
high in the air but safe landing and
only a single run,
eight for two.
Still the the fight is on between these
two big uh teams.
36 to chase in three overs
and that's high in the air.
They're going for two runs and they'll
get it.
>> 26 runs needed from eight balls. Need a
couple of big hits.
Incoming two balls
down the track. Looking to play
completely missed it.
Very good bowling from Amul Takur. Just
conceded three runs and five balls.
That's hit hard, but there's a very good
stop by the fieldder.
Excellent work. Good throw. A quick
throw. Quick reflexes
and only four runs from Amul Takuro.
Wow, good bowling.
So, one over remaining and 25 to get.
It's very difficult uh to get that 25
runs in last six balls.
So, welcome back once again. You're
watching ICSA Lombard presents Brokers
Premier League 2026 season 3
Saturday cricketing vibes. Saturday and
Sunday cricketing day the excitement
begins.
And that's a famous tagline created by
the team. Hit it big score it bigger. 16
teams for the Dwan glory.
We are already from group A.
Pink Panthers qualified in the
qualifying stage in group A
and admmit Titans. In group B we have
Prodent Warriors
and Hen and let's see talking about
group C now in progress
who will get that quarterfinal ticket.
It's almost now the game of
ace diamonds.
It's ace diamonds already
going towards that victory. That's a
very good bowling. Completely missed it.
And after this match may I request the
team Anandrati United captain to come
for the toss with one is1 team captain
for the toss.
Jos Kabos,
Anandrai United
and one L1 team.
Toss boss. And who will call and who
will spin? Heads
is a call
again. Toss
tails. Tails.
Okay. Fielding. They will field first.
And that's it. That's the end of the
match. Wins the victory. Ace Diamond.
They won.
Won by 22 runs. A big margin win. And
coming up
once again, one L1 team. They will.